UNITED UNIVERSITY PROFESSIONS (UUP) RECORDS (APAP039) 1964-2000
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subgroup IV: Office of the Secretary, 1968-1999; 6; 61.73
  - Series 7: Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1967-March 1993; 1977-1988; 6.7; 7.33
    - Indemnification legislation [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1982 May (Box IV.7.4, Folder 6)
    - Independent Commission on the Future of the State University/"The Challenge and the Choice" report [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1987 January (Box IV.7.4, Folder 7)
    - "Innovations in Undergraduate Instruction: Model for the Nineties" (PDQWL co-sponsored conference) [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 April (Box IV.7.4, Folder 8)
    - "Inside Your Schools, The AFT Television Magazine", (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], 1984 July-1985 February (Box IV.7.4, Folder 9)
    - Institute for Research in History, "Scholars in Transition: From the Academy to the Marketplace" program [RESTRICTED], 1983 June-1983 October (Box IV.7.4, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Labor Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1988 June (Box IV.7.4, Folder 11)
    - Joint Labor Management Committees [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box IV.7.4, Folder 12-13)
    - Joint Labor Management Meeting/Workshop [RESTRICTED], 1989 September-1989 October (Box IV.7.4, Folder 14)
    - Journalism Competition [RESTRICTED], 1984 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 15)
    - Kyvig, David (Editor Law, Alcohol and Order: Perspectives on National Prohibition, Drescher contribution: "Labor and Prohibition: The Unappreciated Impact of the Eighteenth Amendment") [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1984 August (Box IV.7.4, Folder 16)
    - Labor Management Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1987 February (Box IV.7.4, Folder 17)
    - Labor-Religion Coalition [RESTRICTED], 1984 January-1985 February; 1989 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 18)
    - Legal (miscellaneous) [RESTRICTED], 1977 March-1987 December (Box IV.7.4, Folder 19)
    - Legal Papers (PERB) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 20)
    - Legislature [RESTRICTED], 1987 January-1989 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 21)
    - Librarians [RESTRICTED], 1986 April (Box IV.7.4, Folder 22)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 23)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 24)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1986 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 25)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 26)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 27)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1990 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 28)
    - Lobbying [RESTRICTED], 1991 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 29)
    - Lobbying-Washington, D.C. [RESTRICTED], 1990 June (Box IV.7.4, Folder 30)
    - Mandatory Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1985 June-1986 June (Box IV.7.4, Folder 31)
    - Martinez, Arsenio P. (grievance) [RESTRICTED], 1983 January-1984 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 32)
    - Mary Muldoon Teacher Assistance Fund (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], 1978 May (Box IV.7.4, Folder 33)
    - Master Plan (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], 1980; 1984 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 34)
    - Medical Emergency Procedures SUNY campuses [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 35)
    - Medical Quadrangle, Inc. (malpractice insurance) [RESTRICTED], 1986 October-1987 August (Box IV.7.4, Folder 36)
    - Member Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1978 May-1981 June (Box IV.7.4, Folder 37)
    - Member Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1983 October-1985 March; 1988 February (Box IV.7.4, Folder 38)
    - Merger-SUNY/CUNY [RESTRICTED], 1977 March; 1979 March (Box IV.7.4, Folder 39)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 40)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 41)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box IV.7.4, Folder 42)
    - Nassau Community College [RESTRICTED], 1984 February-1988 May (Box IV.7.4, Folder 43)
    - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions (Baruch College, CUNY) [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1982 December; 1987 September-1988 October (Box IV.7.4, Folder 44)
    - National Labor Relations Board [RESTRICTED], 1978 March; 1984 March-1984 May (Box IV.7.5, Folder 1)
    - NEA (National Education Association) [RESTRICTED], 1973 June; 1973 November; 1976 March-1979 August (Box IV.7.5, Folder 2)
    - New York Frontlash [RESTRICTED], 1984 September (Box IV.7.5, Folder 3)
    - New York Library Association [RESTRICTED], 1982 April (Box IV.7.5, Folder 4)
    - New York State Public Sector Coalition on Health Care Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1990 May (Box IV.7.5, Folder 5)
    - New Youth Connections [RESTRICTED], 1984 December (Box IV.7.5, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter Editors [RESTRICTED], 1983 September; 1987 March (Box IV.7.5, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Articles [RESTRICTED], 1978-1988 (Box IV.7.5, Folder 8)
    - Nurse Membership [RESTRICTED], 1982 January-1982 February (Box IV.7.5, Folder 9)
    - OSHA [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box IV.7.5, Folder 10-11)
    - PACE (Project for Adult College Education)/UUP Economic Development Project [RESTRICTED], 1978-1987; 4 folders (Box IV.7.5, Folder 12-15)
    - Patent Policy/Computer Software Policy (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], 1986 October; 1987 January-1987 August (Box IV.7.5, Folder 16)
    - PDQWL Leave Applications [RESTRICTED], 1993 January-1993 March (Box IV.7.5, Folder 17)
    - Performance Evaluations [RESTRICTED], 1979 March-1980 March (Box IV.7.5, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases and UUP Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1978 August-1978 December; 1982 August (Box IV.7.5, Folder 19)
    - Professional Staff Congress [RESTRICTED], 1978 May-1984 January (Box IV.7.5, Folder 20)
    - Professional Staff Congress [RESTRICTED], 1984 March-1988 October; 1990 January; 1993 February-1993 March (Box IV.7.5, Folder 21)
    - Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1981 September (Box IV.7.5, Folder 22)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1982 October-1984 October (Box IV.7.5, Folder 23)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1984 December-1985 May (Box IV.7.5, Folder 24)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1985 June-1986 May (Box IV.7.5, Folder 25)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1986 June-1987 January (Box IV.7.5, Folder 26)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1987 February-1988 December; 1991 August (Box IV.7.5, Folder 27)
    - Public Employees Federation [RESTRICTED], 1977 November-1988 July (Box IV.7.5, Folder 28)
    - Public Relations [RESTRICTED], 1979 February-1987 January (Box IV.7.5, Folder 29)
    - Reclassification [RESTRICTED], 1987 August-1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 1)
    - Reclassification [RESTRICTED], 1987 June-1988 April; 2 folders (Box IV.7.6, Folder 2-3)
    - Reclassification (?) Teaching Hospital position descriptions [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box IV.7.6, Folder 4)
    - Reclassification-Albany [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 5)
    - Reclassification-Alfred [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 November (Box IV.7.6, Folder 6)
    - Reclassification-Binghamton [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 7)
    - Reclassification-Brooklyn HSC [RESTRICTED], 1987 April-1987 December (Box IV.7.6, Folder 8)
    - Reclassification-Buffalo HSC [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 9)
    - Reclassification-Buffalo State [RESTRICTED], 1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 10)
    - Reclassification-Buffalo SUNY [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 11)
    - Reclassification-Canton [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 12)
    - Reclassification-Central Administration [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box IV.7.6, Folder 13)
    - Reclassification-Cobleskill [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box IV.7.6, Folder 14)
    - Reclassification-Cortland [RESTRICTED], 1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 15)
    - Reclassification-Delhi [RESTRICTED], 1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 16)
    - Reclassification-Empire State [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 17)
    - Reclassification-Environmental Science and Forestry [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 18)
    - Reclassification-Farmingdale [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box IV.7.6, Folder 19)
    - Reclassification-Fredonia [RESTRICTED], 1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 20)
    - Reclassification-Geneseo [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 21)
    - Reclassification-Maritime [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 22)
    - Reclassification-Morrisville [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 23)
    - Reclassification-New Paltz [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 24)
    - Reclassification-Old Westbury [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 25)
    - Reclassification-Oneonta [RESTRICTED], 1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 26)
    - Reclassification-Optometry [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 27)
    - Reclassification-Oswego [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 28)
    - Reclassification-Plattsburgh [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 November (Box IV.7.6, Folder 29)
    - Reclassification-Potsdam [RESTRICTED], 1987 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 30)
    - Reclassification-Purchase [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1987 December (Box IV.7.6, Folder 31)
    - Reclassification-Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], 1987 November (Box IV.7.6, Folder 32)
    - Reclassification-Stony Brook HSC [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1987 November (Box IV.7.6, Folder 33)
    - Reclassification-Syracuse HSC [RESTRICTED], 1987 July-1987 August (Box IV.7.6, Folder 34)
    - Reclassification-Utica/Rome [RESTRICTED], 1987 September (Box IV.7.6, Folder 35)
    - Reindustrialization [RESTRICTED], 1981 February-1982 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 36)
    - Rensselarville Institute [RESTRICTED], 1984 May (Box IV.7.6, Folder 37)
    - Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1977 November-1982 May (Box IV.7.6, Folder 38)
    - Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1982 June-1989 May (Box IV.7.6, Folder 39)
    - Retrenchment [RESTRICTED], 1978-1985; 1991 (Box IV.7.6, Folder 40)
    - Retrenchment [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box IV.7.6, Folder 41)
    - Retrenchment-SUNY at Albany Report of the Select Committee on Academic Program Priorities [RESTRICTED], 1975 May (Box IV.7.6, Folder 42)
    - Retrenchment-University at Albany Report of the Presidential Task Force on Priorities and Resources [RESTRICTED], 1976 February-1976 March (Box IV.7.6, Folder 43)
    - Safety and Health Correspondence (miscellaneous) [RESTRICTED], 1985 October-1987 March (Box IV.7.6, Folder 44)
    - Salary [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983; 1988 October (Box IV.7.6, Folder 45)
    - Saturn Project [RESTRICTED], 1985 March-1985 April (Box IV.7.6, Folder 46)
    - Senate Professional Association [RESTRICTED], 1972 March (Box IV.7.6, Folder 47)
    - Sex Discrimination/Sexual Harassment [RESTRICTED], 1980 April-1982 March (Box IV.7.6, Folder 48)
    - Sick Leave [RESTRICTED], 1977 June (Box IV.7.6, Folder 49)
    - SIDS (dentists) [RESTRICTED], 1986 August-1987 March (Box IV.7.6, Folder 50)
    - South African Divestiture [RESTRICTED], 1985 May-1987 January (Box IV.7.6, Folder 51)
    - State Aid [to education] [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box IV.7.6, Folder 52)
    - State Comptroller; Payroll & Audit, Division of Audit and Control-Agency Fee, Dues Structure [RESTRICTED], 1977 August-1992 August (Box IV.7.6, Folder 52A)
    - State Employee Federated Appeal (SEFA) [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1988 February (Box IV.7.6, Folder 53)
    - Statutory Tenure Bill [RESTRICTED], 1983 March (Box IV.7.6, Folder 54)
    - "Stephens' Report"-"SUNY 1975-1982 A Budgetary Battle of Access Versus Quality" by Willis H. Stephens, ranking minority member Assembly Ways and Means Committee, et al [RESTRICTED], 1982 June (Box IV.7.6, Folder 55)
    - Stewards' Handbook/UUP Department Rep Handbook [RESTRICTED], 1981 January-1981 February (Box IV.7.6, Folder 56)
    - Stipends-Article 25 [RESTRICTED], 1979 September; 1980 February (Box IV.7.6, Folder 57)
    - Student Association of the State University (SASU) [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1982 October (Box IV.7.7, Folder 0)
    - Student Association of the State University (SASU) [RESTRICTED], 1983 March-1986 June (Box IV.7.7, Folder 1)
    - Student Association of the State University (SASU) [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1990 November (Box IV.7.7, Folder 2)
    - Student Discipline, Positive Approaches to (SUNY publication) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 3)
    - Student Recruitment '82 [RESTRICTED], 1981 July-1981 December; 1984 August (Box IV.7.7, Folder 4)
    - Summer Salaries [RESTRICTED], 1980 March-1981 August (Box IV.7.7, Folder 5)
    - Summer School [RESTRICTED], 1972 March-1977 January (Box IV.7.7, Folder 6)
    - SUNY Alliance and SUNY Alliance Reporter (NEA/NYEA and SUNY-AAUP organization/publication) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 7)
    - SUNY Alumni Association [RESTRICTED], 1981 October-1982 April (Box IV.7.7, Folder 8)
    - SUNY Authors [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 9)
    - SUNY's Best [RESTRICTED], 1989-1992 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 10)
    - SUNY Bronx Tour '85 [RESTRICTED], 1985 March-1985 April (Box IV.7.7, Folder 11)
    - SUNY Economic Impact [RESTRICTED], 1984 February-1984 April (Box IV.7.7, Folder 12)
    - SUNY Hospital Reorganization [RESTRICTED], 1984 October (Box IV.7.7, Folder 13)
    - SUNY in the News [RESTRICTED], 1979 Summer (Box IV.7.7, Folder 14)
    - SUNY-public opinion [RESTRICTED], 1980 October (Box IV.7.7, Folder 15)
    - SUNY Women's Council [RESTRICTED], 1986 July; 1987 February (Box IV.7.7, Folder 16)
    - SUNYCAP (State University of New York College Admissions Personnel) [RESTRICTED], 1985 March (Box IV.7.7, Folder 17)
    - SUNYLA (State University of New York Librarians Association) [RESTRICTED], 1978 June-1987 July (Box IV.7.7, Folder 18)
    - "T" (miscellaneous) [RESTRICTED], 1984 June; 1988 April (Box IV.7.7, Folder 19)
    - Task Force on Women's Safety [RESTRICTED], 1980 December (Box IV.7.7, Folder 20)
    - Tax [RESTRICTED], 1979-1988; 2 folders (Box IV.7.7, Folder 21-22)
    - Tentative Agreement 1979-1982 Contract [RESTRICTED], 1979 June (Box IV.7.7, Folder 23)
    - TIAA/CREF [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 24)
    - TIAA/CREF [RESTRICTED], 1984 June-1987 January (Box IV.7.7, Folder 25)
    - "Tillinghast Report" (proposed plan-malpractice insurance) [RESTRICTED], 1988 March (Box IV.7.7, Folder 26)
    - Tuition Assistance Program (experimental) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 27)
    - Tuition Assistance Program (experimental), Campus Administration [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 28)
    - Tuition Tax Credit Facts [RESTRICTED], ca. 1978-1981 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 29)
    - Tuition Waiver Situations [RESTRICTED], 1984 November-1985 January (Box IV.7.7, Folder 30)
    - Unemployment Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box IV.7.7, Folder 31)
    - Union Health Care Coop [RESTRICTED], 1986 September-1987 July (Box IV.7.7, Folder 32)
    - Unionmutual (UUP Group Life Insurance) [RESTRICTED], 1978 March-1978 November (Box IV.7.7, Folder 33)
    - Unit Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1979 June-1983 February (Box IV.7.7, Folder 34)
    - United College Employees (UCE) of Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT) [RESTRICTED], 1981 December-1983 September; 1985 November-1986 May (Box IV.7.7, Folder 35)
    - United Farmworkers [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1989 April (Box IV.7.7, Folder 36)
    - United Federation of Teachers [RESTRICTED], 1978 December-1987 October (Box IV.7.7, Folder 37)
    - United Paperworkers International Union [RESTRICTED], 1988 March (Box IV.7.7, Folder 38)
    - United Way of New York [RESTRICTED], 1985 August-1985 September (Box IV.7.7, Folder 39)
    - universitas [RESTRICTED], 1978 September-1979 November (Box IV.7.7, Folder 40)
    - Vietnam Veterans Memorial addition honoring women [RESTRICTED], 1987 December (Box IV.7.7, Folder 41)
    - Voice [RESTRICTED], 1978 January-1987 May (Box IV.7.7, Folder 42)
    - VOTE/COPE [RESTRICTED], 1979 June; 1991 March; 1992 August (Box IV.7.7, Folder 43)
    - Voucher Policy [RESTRICTED], 1978 February; 1990 October (Box IV.7.7, Folder 44)
    - "W" (miscellaneous) [RESTRICTED], 1980 October-1980 November; 1984 February (Box IV.7.7, Folder 45)
    - Welfare Trust Fund [RESTRICTED], 1979 March-1979 April (Box IV.7.7, Folder 46)
    - Wellness Work Group [RESTRICTED], 1985 November (Box IV.7.8, Folder 1)
    - Wellness Work Group [RESTRICTED], 1986 July-1986 September (Box IV.7.8, Folder 2)
    - Work in America Institute [RESTRICTED], 1986 January-1986 February (Box IV.7.8, Folder 3)
    - Workers Compensation [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986 (Box IV.7.8, Folder 4)
    - Workshop-Parliamentary Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1992 January 31 (Box IV.7.8, Folder 5)
    - Xerox [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1980 June (Box IV.7.8, Folder 6)
    - Yeshiva Decision [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986 (Box IV.7.8, Folder 7)
    - YWCA Tribute to Women [Nuala Drescher is one of women honored] [RESTRICTED], 1984 May (Box IV.7.8, Folder 8)
  - Series 8: Affiliate Conventions, 1976 January-1994 July; 6.8; 3.0
    UUP is affiliated with New York State United Teachers, the American Federation of Teachers, and the AFL-CIO. UUP's President has at times been a vice president of the AFT and served on its Executive Council, as well as on the Board of Directors of NYSUT. In addition, UUP sends representatives to the annual NYSUT Representative Assembly, the biennial AFT convention, and the biennial New York State AFL-CIO convention. Only a few officers attend the AFL-CIO conventions, while a substantial number of delegates are elected to attend the RAs and AFT conventions as representatives of UUP.
    The materials in this series relate to the conventions of these affiliates and include mailings to all UUP delegates regarding the convention details including administrative information such as hotel accommodations and travel arrangements, as well as correspondence regarding UUP resolutions to be proposed at the conventions. Also included are the materials that the affiliate distributes in connection with the convention, including booklets with proposed resolutions, agendas, promotional literature about programs sponsored by it and/or benefits offered by it, a copy of its constitution, listings of delegates, budget reports, officer reports, daily summaries of proceedings, and news articles or reports relating to key topics of concern. In some instances, particularly in the Reilly years (for which the most information is available), a separate file is included which contains Reilly's copies of some of the UUP and affiliate-distributed materials annotated by him, as well as occasional handwritten notes. The Secretary's files contain the more administrative and logistical materials.
    The records in this series provide an opportunity to examine UUP's interactions with its affiliates in statewide education (NYSUT), education nationally (AFT) and organized labor statewide (AFL-CIO) and the various resolutions it has sought to have adopted by each organization. Additional materials relating to affiliate conventions can be found in the Secretaries' Files, Series 6 of this Subgroup, while materials dealing with the more direct relationship between UUP and its affiliates, such correspondence between UUP and the leadership of these affiliates, can be found in the various subject and correspondence series in this collection. Consult the index to the box and folder list for the exact locations.
    - AFL-CIO (NYS) Convention 1988-Secretary's files/AFL-CIO distributed materials, 1988 July-1988 August; 2 folders (Box IV.8.1, Folder 1-2)
    - AFL-CIO (NYS) Convention 1990-Secretary's files/AFL-CIO distributed materials, 1990 June-1990 August (Box IV.8.1, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO (NYS) Convention 1990-AFL-CIO distributed materials, 1990 August; 2 folders (Box IV.8.1, Folder 4-5)
    - AFL-CIO (NYS) Convention 1992-Secretary's files/AFL-CIO distributed materials, 1992 August (Box IV.8.1, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO (NYS) Convention 1992-AFL-CIO distributed materials, 1992 August; 2 folders (Box IV.8.1, Folder 7-8)
    - AFT Convention 1979, 1979 March-1979 June (Box IV.8.1, Folder 9)
    - AFT Convention 1980, 1980 April-1980 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 10)
    - AFT Convention 1981, 1981 March-1981 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 11)
    - AFT Convention 1982, 1982 February-1983 January (Box IV.8.1, Folder 12)
    - AFT Convention 1983-Drescher File, 1983 January-1983 August (Box IV.8.1, Folder 13)
    - AFT Convention 1983, 1983 March-1983 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 14)
    - AFT Convention 1984, 1984 June-1984 August (Box IV.8.1, Folder 15)
    - AFT Convention 1986, 1986 January-1986 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 16)
    - AFT Convention 1988-Reilly's files, 1988 March-1988 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 17)
    - AFT Convention 1988-Secretary's files, 1988 March-1988 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 18)
    - AFT Convention 1988-AFT distributed materials, 1988 July; 2 folders (Box IV.8.1, Folder 19-20)
    - AFT-Second Biennial Conference Higher Education and Economic Development, 1989 February (Box IV.8.1, Folder 21)
    - AFT Convention 1990-Reilly's files, 1990 April-1990 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 22)
    - AFT Convention 1990-Secretary's files, 1990 March-1990 July (Box IV.8.1, Folder 23)
    - AFT Convention 1990-AFT distributed materials, 1990 July; 2 folders (Box IV.8.1, Folder 24-25)
    - AFT Convention 1992-Reilly's files, 1992 August (Box IV.8.1, Folder 26)
    - AFT Convention 1992-Secretary's files, 1992 May-1992 August (Box IV.8.2, Folder 1)
    - AFT Convention 1992-AFT distributed materials, 1992 August; 2 folders (Box IV.8.2, Folder 2-3)
    - AFT Convention 1994-Secretary's files, 1994 March-1994 July (Box IV.8.2, Folder 4)
    - AFT Convention 1994-AFT distributed materials, 1994 July (Box IV.8.2, Folder 5)
    - AFT-QuEST (Quality Educational Standards in Teaching) Conferences, 1981; 1983; 1985; 1987 (Box IV.8.2, Folder 6)
    - AFT-QuEST (Quality Educational Standards in Teaching) Conference, 1989 (Box IV.8.2, Folder 7)
    - NYSUT, AFT, NEA Conventions 1976-ballots, 1976 January (Box IV.8.2, Folder 8)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1978, 1978 February-1978 March (Box IV.8.2, Folder 9)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1979, 1979 February-1979 April (Box IV.8.2, Folder 10)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1980, 1980 January-1980 March (Box IV.8.2, Folder 11)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1981, 1980 December-1981 June (Box IV.8.2, Folder 12)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1982, 1982 February-1982 October (Box IV.8.2, Folder 13)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1983, 1982 November-1983 May (Box IV.8.2, Folder 14)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1983-NYSUT distributed materials, 1983 April (Box IV.8.2, Folder 15)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1984, 1983 December-1984 March (Box IV.8.2, Folder 16)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1985, 1984 October-1985 April (Box IV.8.2, Folder 17)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1986, 1986 January-1986 March (Box IV.8.2, Folder 18)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1987, 1987 February-1987 April; 2 folders (Box IV.8.2, Folder 19-20)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1988-Reilly files, 1988 February-1988 May (Box IV.8.2, Folder 21)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1988-Secretary's files, 1988 February-1988 July; 2 folders (Box IV.8.2, Folder 22-23)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1988-NYSUT distributed materials, 1988 May; 2 folders (Box IV.8.2, Folder 24-25)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1989-Reilly's files, 1989 February-1989 March (Box IV.8.2, Folder 26)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1989-Secretary's files, 1988 December-1989 April (Box IV.8.2, Folder 27)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1989-Secretary's files-Resolutions, 1989 January-1989 April (Box IV.8.3, Folder 1)
    - NYSUT Representative Assembly 1989-NYSUT distributed materials, 1989 April; 2 folders (Box IV.8.3, Folder 2-3)